{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/51622505","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51622505","name":"Ford Field- Suite Kitchens","address":"2000 Brush","zipcode":"48201","owner":"","licenseNumber":"218005","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"335","coords":"-83.04562,42.33984","geojson":{"id":"51622505","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.045622135,42.339842961]},"properties":{"name":"Ford Field- Suite Kitchens","owner":"","address":"2000 Brush","zipcode":"48201","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"Medium","license_number":"218005","establishmentid":"51622505","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"335","most_recent_license_date":"29/4/2022"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"4259","name":"Ford Field- Third Floor Concessions","address":"2000 Brush","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4260","name":"Ford Field- Employee Lounge","address":"2000 Brush","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4257","name":"Ford Field- First Floor Concessions","address":"2000 Brush","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4258","name":"Ford Field- Second Floor Concessions","address":"2000 Brush","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4255","name":"Ford Field- Levy Rest. (Main Kitchen)","address":"2000 Brush","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"2290","name":"Ford Field","address":"2000 Brush","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"2335","name":"Ah! Moore' Cafe","address":"2000 Brush Ste 200","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"3900","name":"Gateway Deli","address":"2000 Brush","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"4256","name":"Ford Field- Corner Lounge","address":"2000 Brush","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4261","name":"Ford Field- Food Portables","address":"2000 Brush","zipcode":"48226"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"57331","inspectionDate":"2021-12-05T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-301.14","violationDescription":"Ventilation hood systems and devices shall be sufficient in number and capacity to prevent grease or condensation from collecting on walls and ceilings.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Ventilation hood","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Under the Hood","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"49283","inspectionDate":"2019-09-29T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.114","violationDescription":"A chemical SANITIZER used in a SANITIZING solution for a manual or\nmechanical operation shall meet these limits or as otherwise approved: (P)\n\tChlorine        ppm           pH<10             pH<8\n\t\t      25              120 F              120 F\n\t\t      50              100 F              75 F\n\t\t     100              55 F               55 F\n                 Iodine           a concentration of between 12.5 and 25 ppm and minimum temp of 75 F and pH of 5 or less or meets manufacturer's specifications. (P)\n\n                Quats            minimum temperature of 75 F, hardness of 500 ppm or less and meet manufacturers use directions. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Quaternary ammonia solution","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Below 100 ppm","subProblem":"","location":"THREE COMPARTMENT SINK","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"THREE COMPARTMENT SINK","subLocation":"Above the Test strips","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"ICE CREAM MACHINE","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2010-01-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair"}]},{"inspectionid":"43681","inspectionDate":"2018-10-07T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"THREE COMPARTMENT SINK","subLocation":"Above the Test strips","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"4-904.11","violationDescription":"(A) SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES and cleaned and SANITIZED UTENSILS shall be handled, displayed, and dispensed so that contamination of FOOD- and lip-contact surfaces is prevented.   \n(B) Knives, forks, and spoons that are not prewrapped shall be presented so that only the handles are touched by EMPLOYEES and by CONSUMERS if CONSUMER self-service is provided.   \n(C) Except as specified under ¶ (B) of this section, SINGLE-SERVICE ARTICLES that are intended for FOOD- or lip-contact shall be furnished for CONSUMER self-service with the original individual wrapper intact or from an APPROVED dispenser.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Kitchenware and tableware","subItem":"sanitized utensils spoons","problemDescription":"Allows for contamination of food-contact/lip-contact surfaces","subProblem":"During dispensing","location":"DISH ROOM","subLocation":"Utensils","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2010-01-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Handle so as to prevent contamination."},{"violationCode":"4-901.11","violationDescription":"After cleaning and SANITIZING, EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS shall be air-dried or used after adequate draining.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Clean equipment and utensil(s)","subItem":"utensils","problemDescription":"Stored/stacked wet","subProblem":"","location":"DISH ROOM","subLocation":"Utensils","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Completely air dry all items prior to storage/use."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"ICE CREAM MACHINE","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair"},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"FLOOR","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"hair/beard net","problemDescription":"Not worn on head/hair","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"Hair Restraints/Covering","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide hat or hair net."}]},{"inspectionid":"41076","inspectionDate":"2017-12-16T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Hot food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored below 135 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"At the Hot holding temperatures","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2012-01-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store above 135 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"FLOOR","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"39593","inspectionDate":"2017-08-14T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-13T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51622505"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}